Hello hi friends welcome to our channel today
we will talk about Super Star Plus plan
first we will see
what is Super Sir Plus plan why you
should take it or how you should take it, that is
what should be the reference, we will
discuss about that after that
we moved towards basic details and main features
that before starting the video I would
like to tell you that if you have come to my channel for the first
time then you can subscribe to my channel
I keep
bringing videos related to investment insurance and mutual fund daily
so subscribe to it friends let's move
ahead in the video voice up Sir
Plus if you feel that your existing understanding is
not edited that means you have reduced two or
three lock screen locks your existing
mediclaim is already you feel that it is
too less for me but you have to increase your understanding
but if you increase your existing mediclaim then the
premium is very high that is why you are
increasing it for so long then
this is the best solution to
buy Super Splendor
you can buy Super Splendor from any company  It is not
that the mediclaim you have
is already from SBI or any other
company, government company, private company, it does
not make any difference, or if you have a
policy from your bank in a group policy, it does
not make any difference, you can take a super
surplus policy from any company,
I am talking about specific
rockstar here, on top of that
you get less premium in it and there are
lots of benefits about which we will
discuss in this video, first let me
talk about this that this
policy is good for those who have a low budget, it is not that
only you have already mediclaim, you
can take this policy, if you do this,
first of all, whatever is the defined limit, whatever is the existing
limit, if the limit is 3 lakhs, then
even if you bear the expenses of 3 lakhs yourself,
you can take this policy, I discussed this premium
calculation for short-term starting, so that
you will get some idea about
how cheap this policy is and what
we have put here is the editable duty.
Friends, the company assumes that
you have an existing mediclaim of this
amount and on top of that, it will give you star
health cover. Here I have taken three
examples of deductible and how much will this amount be, that is,
of this policy,
I will write here for you, here the
flex period is remaining and
if you have a deductible of three lakhs, that is, if you have an emergency
mediclaim of 3 lakhs, then your premium will be
only 5581 inclusive of GST premium,
friends, this is the final premium that you have to pay,
which is also higher,
3245. You have given a breakup of individual plan, if there will be a
family plan here,
then a little more is not included in the program,
friends, so if you are
searching that you
need mediclaim coverage of three lakhs, or up to 25 lakhs, that
too at a low premium, then this is your solution,
friends, in 5581 you get front flex
coverage, if the meeting time is more on OLX graph, then
your premium gets reduced a little,
4466.60 effective  In your 24 ms word,
you need more cover up to 25 lakhs and
Pramod Yadav's premium is 3351. In short,
if I tell you that from your existing
understanding, when there is one seat, then you get the
policy rule on time, so this is the
benefit of taking the policy, which is that
you get a good advantage in low premium.
Now let us start with its basic details.
If I tell you the basic details, then this
is a topper policy.
You get this cover in two variants, Silver and Gold. The
plan that I told you was of the round plan, so
you should be carefree. It is not that the
premium will be higher in it. Open my app and
tell me the premium of the plan. If we
talk about celebrity in the beginning, then ATM 265. Anyone
can take it if the
limit of 10 dependents or child is the same as
normal, zero till 2030, that
payment will be 10 percent.
If you are on the enrollment page, then if I
talk about reversal, then the option of life-long renewal is
available to you in this.  This is the policy term,
one year has been made available to you in this,
free medical screening is
not required in this, this is a big point
friends, so your support will be 5055,
so in normal mediclaim you are exempted from
Medicare medical test,
but here on taking the topper policy, no
medical screening is required till 1658,
one of its advantages goes beyond the main features,
friends, if I
talk about the main features, then here
if you look at the silver plate, there
is a limit of 4000 birthdays and more golden direction has been given,
which I had
shared with you before folding the procedures, there is
a big advantage in both, if we talk about this entire post
relation, then here in silver
3168, coverage of 60 is available in gold,
this is a big advantage and here
you have a limit, if you subscribe to the channel, I am being
told
how much you can keep, so on the silver
side you have the option of keeping a deductible of 3 and 5 lakhs
What is deductible, let me
repeat it. If the concept is
not clear to you then the company considers
your existing mediclaim as deductible, which
you have to
tell. Your existing mediclaim is 3 lakh or
3 lakh. Let us assume that the company will provide you cover up to 10 lakh on top of that.
I am talking about the silver plan. If you take the gold plan, then
the maximum to inflict is available,
which I told you in the premium sharing.
If you take 3 lakh, 5 lakh, 10
lakh, the deductible, that year's premium
also varies. So you are getting all this. If I
talk about the six point options, then I have covered these multiple points for you.
Road, ambulance, air ambulance,
delivery expenses, recharge benefit,
all these are being given under the fold.
Repeat inside the gold plan and the waiting
period is star marked because you should
also understand that there is a huge difference between the silver and gold plans,
meaning this
quit wife initial will be given to you in the third gold plan.
They have a strong meeting, in general
both are 30s for you but for specific diseases
you have a daily waiting period of 4 months
in silver but in gold only 12 months
direct person has given you less oh
existing digit director you have got four
times less here it means in 12 months
you will also get printed so that will also be
covered for you in super top up line so this
was a lot of benefits for above problem
so how did you like this plan tell me if
you want to purchase from me then you
can contact me I have given the contact number
in the description it can be applied here also so that is why
I am giving 7023 2483 label
process friends the purchase of win world
cup policy is done if you do
not have pimples then if pimples are there then it takes two to three
days after approval so
friends if you liked this video then
like it and share it
with your friends and subscribe to
our channel I post such
investment insurance and mutual fund daily  I keep
bringing related videos, thank you
friends, thank you for watching my video.